hi welcome back to the at home retreat
Tsingtao jumping up on quite your life
will quite do that there's I call it
online retreat sometimes I call it at
home retreat at home retreat sounds more
friendly no heat or narlikar to to be no
heat or no lakitu ties there but 2008
and in her new chrome and the picture we
have here is somebody shooting an arrow
looking jump a called a lie down
badminton and the name of today's class
is called arrows and factories they will
have my own nail and you then Banyan
yummy and I want to teach you an
important Tibetan word before we start
once I got to think they that quant
don't don't don't a chelate pants a kilo
pen means to shoot an arrow or to throw
a spear hand Gong in lab but then Hawk
feel more not now
and oftentimes in books about karma you
hear about a thing Stanley knows about
it called tau equals like being near
capital gamma mu do Stanley bit don't I
know develop and say kill a and this is
the Karma that you do now which is going
to throw your next life it's going to
decide what is your next day like
melambe learn same name but keeps out go
back now sacred day keeps out woke up at
la z
so like if you're a very good person in
this life Mohammed murder
don't give me you'll make karma which
will shoot you into the future life as a
human again man set out on the machine
name kappa epic epsilon mu mu Leonora
and then usually they say there's two
Carmen's called Pangea keel a which is
the throwing come on go hang a blue girl
a pentakill a doll and give parasitizing
and then there's zouk taquile which
means finishing class or a chelate
niolani upon tea and they always compare
it in the ancient books to a master
painter and his student painters maja
lumens are saying our town USA Camuto
has impact ironic out rock well I
so the master Paynter will take in the
old days they will take a piece of
charcoal and there was sketched like if
you're painting a person they will
sketch all the person but namelessly but
playing a sous la mort and ah-ha-ha-ha
long you know Cabana in wooden warehouse
if I had done but we da
so that's called that's like throwing
Carmen like it decided you will be a
human being
right now Sonia parasitizing Nordic we
think about Salem economy but what's the
details of your new life
young if you go get some work about
Lizzy will you be rich will you be poor
but is now hang you will you beat all
will you be sure about sick cow hype huh
will you be a woman will you be my boss
and namhae new then in the metaphor the
student painters that the master says
paint this part blue paint this part
yellow paint this part green here jump
and a new scene being Hawk Van Looy tiny
no longer for name wasn't yet elevate
for name or bang with a name or sang
like a
and in Tibetan that's called so late
that night so that's the Karma which
fills in the details of your life which
is thrown by destroying me but darling
we have muscle and a cockatiel cuckoo
clock up back mandu tickly boy yep teres
enticing
now the reason I mentioned those two is
I think I've discussed them before in
the lemon in this lemon series by the
Lisa methodically $90 to get onto the
talent we jumped on by Sam Landrum
blooped I talked to a young lamb bloom
night but so far this series took ten
years okay you need major yz9 that kills
I'm Windham and to be honest I don't
remember what I taught you I didn't try
I think that monoi Pocoyo does a Jose
Caban you do see but what I want to say
today is this is not destroying Karma
that I taught you before you know him my
lad back home Fulani a parasitizing
Matilda's like a pan today
before the throwing karma and the
details karma were called Pangea Kili
and sob tequila too long yep
parasitizing when you tip develop ends a
key levels of psyche lay
yeah and now we have a slightly
different word which is pentakill a and
Dubcek president Okimoto ha ha clapping
say kilowatt you particular
the first kind of karma is is the same
you can think of a spear or an arrow
Rangi blue teal a new yoga pant gotta
give a more not down with ten
but the duplicate layer I don't want you
to think of student painters use up like
a light document of money because even
halfway
I want you to think of a factory one go
but you may move yeah my they do a lot
of things and then a car comes out of
the factory I'll am letting you to buy
so Dom would you say how it looks as
soon
okay let's read the text and then you'll
be more comfortable I had often been
Mossad or capacitate on my own
attacked and Daniella - Nikki your lap a
Muslim name so you really have to get
familiar with these 12 lengths of the
dependency take a battle suit for lamb
when when we hang in DNA
muscle means you should be able if I say
what's link number 3 what's Lee number 5
you should be able to say immediately
what the onions Isabella's in unison am
logic about psychotic Nora - I see my
teacher made us memorize it / - Toa
black America
Eponine - taquile sunburn option Shiva
miso soup arepa sorry nah-nah per
teacher cooperate but the birds are kept
a super Cooper number 2 / sip - chip
Akira juni but that she you know we had
to say it now then he'll say what's that
one I hope you guys will do that now
after you know all the traveling like
individual friends basis how betta can
we hang in June you knew about Canyon
or individual enemies actually Kato
Canyon took suit you like sure do look
sugar you should be familiar with how
these are grouped into groups
Neelam when we got my June looking young
like tank that young
and there are four groups black are born
young now if you're studying the Tibetan
and you're following the Tibetan when
you go back now you didn't take that
back about now peers often didn't date
that I want to say unfortunately full
moon night that Tom Milan the word in
Tibetan yen lack in the word in Sanskrit
anger so don't think they attack young
larvae do something fun ELISA they are
the same word for the links and the same
word for the groups la Camuto Japan
genuine bikumu to Japan young
so I'm gonna use this s's don't cut the
line now so you don't because Matt's a
convenient so there are four groups of
links carbonium nutrient first one is
called Peggy and overlap is a that's the
shooting darling young banku
second is the islands of Lake easily
that's the factory girl darling um yeah
my hi baby yeah like means what was
shocked that like you can say the arrow
pump a to praise Allah Kanye landings
Edith ban tobacco tin or lamb with them
so Group one is kind of like the Archer
no more long young women come and Group
three is kind of like the random bands
of new Mouton - it's like the fact you
know new yeah my good for number two
badarian like they it's kind of like
what the factory puts up your bond he's
only using yeah my sons were there so
there you have four groups
we're at Utica bone Yan Aero shooter a
bank owned car producing factory yeah my
son's let's say Hawaii the arrow which
you shoot within my got back button and
the car which comes out of the factory I
take say how it looks i sue
okay they americani seven double the
purport of Bhutan taken a llama do
tickle a nice table and table with them
now if we're going to talk about it in
terms of gardening major noodle pants in
our in our Kalki Koechlin moon
then the first thing we do Dalton
misunderstanding you say it's like the
gardener who plants puts the seed in the
ground
lambu and that half down soon
and the actions you take because you
have misunderstanding lambu because
bankotsu you say karma yep
those are like the seed that's planted
by the garden do dog food you have donut
rumbling I'm good okay now the earth
where you put the sin razor teeth no got
that hot zone it's the first half of
link number 3 which is awareness
sandokan isn't too bad Hachi lesson yet
so when you when you say to your husband
I'm not stupid you're stupid which is
link number evacuate I'm comin I'm comin
open window no onions into her because
you thought to yourself are you doing
Rica but that boy back home and we can
which is lingam knocking Lanyon them
pulling up run I'm not offering him what
time would then go me home choir
then what's link number 3 hey Dom yen's
bubala Z is the mind of the wife in the
kitchen at the time that she says I'm
not stupid you're stupid and she hears
her own words and those words are
imprinted on her mind now let them do
we've worked on you babe that's very dim
McCoy and come hang with no Rocco a
nanny learner would think Oh a random
learner Dobby in sover tum tum tum Coco
I we call that link number 3 you darling
you do to back your mind back at the
moment of planting that came up the
autumn
now the second half of link number 3 is
going to be raised annuity hi Quyen
gentle back the mind after the seat as
the seat opens and goes into the moms
want them to have no nobody bout don't
accompany me
so let's consider these links number one
which is misunderstanding your husband -
um good night Eugene - yep brother su
Hyun sang go jump and then link number 2
which is doing some crap on you and then
we can throw in the first half of
consciousness pass out our mm a muffin
noodle with those two and a half swings
hi I'm Emily onions in dah okay didn't
under shed on zoom in Tibetan it means
if you added another half you would get
three don't know Kanye land knew about
him I'm gonna pick up a sitcom back
about today me right no I think that
dollahyde really these are the archer
day line even cool
okay this two and a half lengths are
canyons in a longer band I'm with pain
and I put an image here of I I grew I
think it's a blue cloud around the
shooting links rather not moving or they
might've a bogey Nalla thambi sang some
questions in Bundy
now we'll go back to the Turks fantastic
one man Sabine Lisicki gamba now you
take that seed sobbing may have some
loss happen and you put on a Jew which
is why not to renew and blue which is
fertilizer Baloo laughing bond and then
first Sherman's you'd make it kind of
wet and warm
that's how dr. sacani like a man's jaw
are called a bap is an ancient word that
means what a mom does to their kid when
they feed them and they take care of
them so camera means these extra things
water fertilizer sunlight they are
supporting the city they are feeding
them to kill a deer my mommy made
language control hockey or two and four
times of to leave I come back on a
landing tooth my own endorphin mornings
I matter to DiNozzo Johanns Oh
so which of the links are like the water
and the fertilizer and the Sun line you
know it's eight and learn
they make the comic seed ready to give a
baby
junkie and have them we have some
sounded John Underwood in Bay
in terms of the death process
now I did for the aquatic jet we can
speak more specifically of the one seed
which is going to be activated to shoot
your next life back okay now go to a
home remote have them master to pick up
the button but gives out huka Pak
and we talked about being very careful
to make the hospital room comfortable
and speak quietly and remind people of
their good deeds but you kinda know if
you could contend a lamb token from
being tuned in timeline when I said my
neck Martin will be via clamp tokoha
so you can explain link 8 and link 9 in
general terms of your whole life you
should do coffee meditation or you
should regret the bad things you did
welcome back kotter is I think in real
time Valentino Chung hua kappa kapap
kapap name to contain cafe Hakka burning
and her venom with so packed that lamb
or you can think of eight and nine more
specifically as the last moment of your
general awareness of this lifetime
before your mind shifted like an animal
rocketing main engine temp at encoding
new laughing huh quick convenient to
chunko back Tom keeps on I took him to
Comanche and sang some new tempo but
when I say last moment of your life your
general awareness of this world shifts
to animal state of mind I don't mean you
become an animal you have animals man I
don't mean people know that cuckoo
cuckoo I got back to my bed hey the
night you and Sam time time to talk but
to Hong Kong et like a panto time will
convert back Coco take homo convert go
conquer a new tenure I mean your mind
dies either let them take a bunch it 99%
of your mind dies in which infant tempt
them to go batshit
and all this left is we call nuke sir
looks about the canyons you can lighten
tagging online yes sir like primeval
mind the mind which you've had for
billions of lifetime's yah
congi and eyes on you thumb to win three
time took my backpack our Tom handy keep
some by the way that's why it's very
difficult to remember what happened in
your past life
Magnum tonight our thoughts our heart in
you doozy desai ratan keep to go back
you can say 99% of your mind died during
that last minute of awareness back
got annoyed admit infant jumped empty
cover back that jet of something a quick
convenient
so that seed in the garden gets its
water and it's fertilizer Patti had
zoomed out on Hoover not turned up on
fun by LinkedIn it's the feet the seat
gets very far nine years Omaha's doctor
named dr. Jung CG make away from popping
is a cheaper and it makes it certain
that that seed is going to throw a new
life value night lamps are not checked
and run has endorsed a book named Wiremu
keep some boy
so therefore link eight nine and ten we
let on Eunji anthem hidden bam boy
these are I like to call them factory
links oh I think I do mulan unions we
know they are producing your new body
and your new mind June damn duck okay
but them took my welcome back by link
ten that new body and mind are almost
ready for shipping gang in June we
market a bottom took my good news and
Sandy but Jin D so again I showed an
image here of link eight nine and ten
and by the way the links are equal to
the old clock see like one two three
four five so eight nine and 10 are gonna
be we're eight nine and ten o'clock toy
that do that moving angered a unions in
time
chin back my banyan today Union long way
you can keep Tomoko long you more
highborn am with hey Tom gin bamboo
Cosell annoying madam ho tea time teen
bamboozled
so we finished the shooting the hunter
Union Bandido yeah mister factory which
is getting you new body in mind I don't
add a hunt duck funnier my madam big
joke about Cote but them two boys and
say now let's go back to the text Rizzo
hey quite like movin back in your
cognition
Jesse turning some children either so
let's go to the moment that the seat
splits open and the spout comes up
Levite I didn't quite come I have no no
revin a mom
this is like the production that comes
out of the factory I know you don't use
an firm look so soon
and that's link number 11 which is your
rebirth I think back now there's gonna
be another production link will come to
it later
by the second movie engines and from cat
you don't a stand-in for docile so if
the factory is the seed already wet and
fertilized
nallamalla has loomed a good pokémon
front son
then the production coming out of the
factory the first part of that
production is your release and from look
so soon find out the inquest and from
now last dicing back and in the image
here you see link number 11 and I've
added truck don't you like about unions
in remote battle that team an engine we
hurry because that's gonna be another
production but it's gonna in the text
it's coming a little bit later buried
our cell emotion from CAC Newton ban ban
now saying I didn't wanna Shepherd
target chained to Tinashe timings so
cheering but then they'll catch a it's
all about a tender chetana
me public Dipper so what's the arrow
that gets shot back I see who's the
shooter do member kyleannie Bunton cut
back on Yoko Ono I thought I he was I
don't go toil among some toys the first
half of link number 3 in my mind is
where where the seed is planted so down
without theand contingent so back come
to kotonoha Matsudo pho now what's the
arrow that gets within banbao like I
know he listed here today the second
half of the back-up plan which is the
mine and trim them to cool then the two
guys in the boat your mind and your body
inside your mother's hang them to
take a bath tongue to comb comb it back
and then you're sent in the contact of
your mind with the outside world because
of those organs so dose it don't talk
with them devotees I've been widely
being exact wonder and in the feelings
you have about that contact that that's
think that's a stickier that food smells
good bad don't you come so my cat Markov
is it don't that dot and uh but we hope
and I would it known actually it should
be
I like that smell or I don't like this
trotty
non a lot ot mudo have both hunting muda
so four and a half of the Lynx leave a
transient boundary either
which is from lamb with end of hunger we
call in Tibetan aircon result links
which are tucked in tight onto the
violin even good cuando Bundy
okay one more small piece here Rowena
gosh it cheating bit then Downey now
let's talk about link number 12 buzzer
hey no I mean Yin you told me hi for $20
hi my don't lie what's the technical
name then get work analogy
yeah yeah sorry
that's with maybe is it thank you
Karla is out with one really does hey
don't laugh my banker Dan Kiki doors for
you we don't like young Lyoko so now
we're talking about three I'm sorry do
make that guy distracted yeah this link
of death and maybe aging good night back
on let's out doing that
that's another credit that we took we
promise you one more production link
right the car that came out of engines
I'm contacting thought they would use
I'm from no don't you die say so that
whole experience of getting old in time
my teeth on Boateng it will be exactly
watch it
is a car which is produced in the
factory of length 8 9 and 10 which is
the fantasy Lamech I say how it looks
and so Tanya micronutrient am in bamboo
jingle I have no filter
okay that's the most boring class I gave
you in this group I think so
lollipop Yamato Duncan I don't eat it
and this is when my friends say just
like can you teach something that we can
really use logic Banton I guess ela
Tecate I do see Dom I don't talk to
sulcata to look how and I apologize that
I don't always show you how there's not
one word of Dharma that you cannot use
okay now beef up Mack about some tase's
ooh
and the older you get the more you
appreciate all the things that people
have taught you which I have many
chicken don't chop the can you do ma
yurid I like a back do master Corrin
knew but because in these last two days
of classes when we talked about the
sections of the wheel of life that kind
of hang together doing fun gourmet sale
annoy Magic Island get right now we are
now in a position to answer an important
question
Nate downloading would go Hawk wanta how
many new dog come back for a session 18
hey way like we're even with them
Thank You Stanley for translating so
happily coming back say levy that feels
like more pepper hateful
you